

- 9013260940
- anjumani2015@gmail.com
- https://anjumani2015.wixsite.com/website-1

#### **EDUCATION**

Masters In Psychology Indira Gandhi Open National University 2023- Present

Bachelor's in History University of Delhi - New Delhi July 2018 to August 2021

## **SKILLS**

- Date Entry
- Recruiting
- Communication skills
- WRITTEN SKILLS
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Adobe Premiere Pro

# **ANJU MANI**

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm Very flexible with my work. I'm a person who is very dedicated and look for growth of the company by providing strategies and solutions. I Have a very good designing skills too. Did a certificate course of 1 year at Red Pixels.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

August 2022 to February 2023Capital
Consultant
HR Recruiter- Freelancing
I worked as an H.R recruiter here.

June 2022 to August 2022Edlodge Foundation

HR Recruiter- Remote

I recruited teachers for the Foundation.

February 2022 to May 2022 Graphic Designer

Made posters and videos for Facebook

June 2021 to Decembar 2021 Futurica Technologies Data Entry Did Data typing on Google worksheet.

### **LANGUAGE**

- English Expert
- Hindi Fluent
- Spanish Beginner
- Korean Beginner